Jason Dugdale

LINKEDIN

uk.linkedin.com/in/jdugdale

LOCATION

San Francisco

Profile

I'm a tech guy who loves talking to customers and helping improve their experience. I enjoy solving tricky tech issues as much as working with customers to help them understand a product, or help me understand what they want to achieve with it

Experience

SUPPORT MANAGER, DATASIFT; READING, UK & SAN FRANCISCO - NOV 2015 - PRESENT (RELOCATED JUL 2017)

- Promoted to Manager of the Global Support Team
- High level of involvement in Product
 Development as a customer advocate;
 working to ensure we were fixing problems
 customers care about
- Played role of "Acting Product Manager" for legacy platform features, determining necessary features and enhancements
- Strong focus on employee happiness and empowerment
- Achieving strong C-Sat ratings; +98% overall, including a 10 month 100% satisfaction streak
- Work to ensure the voice of the customer was heard within the organization
- Manage inbound tickets and outbound communications during platform incidents

LEAD SUPPORT ENGINEER, DATASIFT; READING, UK - NOV 2011 - NOV 2015

- As the first member of DataSift's Client Services team, I built an initial technical support offering in time for the product launch
- Grew the Support Team to six members
- Scaled support organization from early adopters, to 300+ SMB and Enterprise customers
- Trained the Support Team to be capable of handling a wide variety of highly technical to "best practice" questions

RETAIL/RENTAL SHOP LEAD, WHISTLER BLACKCOMB: WHISTLER, BC - NOV 2010 - SEP 2011

- Worked as a team lead in a ski rental and retail shop for the winter
- Responsible for keeping all rental customers safe and happy
- Worked as a bicycle mechanic for the summer
- Responsible for maintaining a fleet of ~250 bicycles across seven locations

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER; REMOTE - JUN 2010 - MAR 2011

• Designed and deployed a series of Wordpress websites for various clients

JR. TECH CONSULTANT, HIRESERVE; READING, UK – JUN 2008 - MAR 2010

- Worked on PL/SQL and Ext-JS web development as an intern
- Took part in a rotating customer support schedule

Education

University of Reading, UK - BSc. Applied Computer Science, 2010

Skills

Ruby, Rails, Python, PHP, SQL, NoSQL, REST APIs, UNIX, JIRA, Zendesk, communicating with customers, incident management and resolution, translating customer issues into use cases for a Product or Dev team